<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="63">

    <author>MEMDOR</author>
    <version>1.2.0.0</version>

    <title>
        <en>Super-Liner 6x4 V2 Auto-Load.</en>
        <de>Super-Liner 6x4 V2 Auto-Lader.</de>
        <fr>Super-Liner 6x4 V2 Chargement Automatique.</fr>
        <it>Super-Liner 6x4 V2 Caricatore Automatico.</it>
    </title>

    <description>
        <en> <![CDATA[
Achimobil "Pallet Autoloader Specialization" is required for the Pallet Autoloader function.

MACK Super-Liner 6x4 V2 with pallet autoloader function makes your work with productions and numerous pallets easier. 
Up to 24 Euro pallets can be transported with one tour. 

The MACK has a trailer hitch, so trailers can be coupled, which increases the amount of Euro pallets to be transported depending on the trailer.

Euro pallets, liquid tanks, BigBag pallets, cotton round bales and oversized Euro pallets can be loaded by the pallet autoloader specialization.

The payload can be selected in the store between 12 and 24 Euro pallets. 
With the color choice you design the MACK according to their wishes.

Changelog V 1.2.0.0
- Tested with TestRunner_public (GIANTS). (Error free!)
- Loading area enlarged
- Loading area adapted for autoload
- Autoload trigger moved further forward because of trailer
- Payload changed 12 and 24 Euro pallets.
- Trailer hitch with connections moved further back. (Autoload now works with trailer).
- Side lights attached.
- Dependencies of "Pallet Autoloader Specialization" added

Changelog V 1.1.0.0
- Tested with TestRunner_public (GIANTS). (Error free!)
- Flatbed adjusted
- Payload changed. 10 and 20 Euro pallets.
- Rear lights attached to the flatbed
- Trailer hitch with connections attached. (Attention, unfortunately the autoload with trailer works only with the truck, not with the trailer!)
- Logos attached to the flatbed
- New store image
- New icon image
- Description in modDesc adapted

Changelog V 1.0.8.0
- Color selection
- Translation moved to the modDesc
            ]]>
        </en>

        <de> <![CDATA[
Für die Funktion des Paletten-Autoloader wird die „Paletten Autoloader Spezialisierung“ von Achimobil benötigt.

MACK Super-Liner 6x4 V2 mit Paletten-Autoloader Funktion erleichter Ihnen die Arbeit mit den Produktionen und den zahlreichen Paletten. 
Bis zu 24 Euro-Paletten können mit einer Tour transportiert werden. 

Der MACK verfügt über eine Anhängerkupplung, so können Anhänger angekoppelt werden, was die Menge der zu transportierenden Euro-Paletten je nach Anhänger steigert.

Euro-Paletten,  Flüssigkeitstanks, BigBag Paletten, Baumwolle Rundballen und übergroße Euro-Paletten können von der Paletten Autoloader Spezialisierung geladen werden.

Die Zuladung kann im Shop zwischen 12 und 24 Euro Paletten gewählt werden. 
Mit der Farbwahl gestalten Sie den MACK nach ihren Wünsche.

Changelog V 1.2.0.0
- Getestet mit TestRunner_public (GIANTS). (Fehlerfrei!)
- Ladefläche vergrößert
- Ladefläche für Autoload angepasst
- Autoload Trigger wegen Anhänger weiter nach vorne verschoben
- Zuladung geänder 12 und 24 Euro Paletten.
- Anhängerkupplung mit Verbindungen weiter nach hinten verlegt. (Autoload funktioniert jetzt mit Anhänger.)
- Seitenlichter angebracht.
- Abhängigkeiten von "Paletten Autoloader Spezialisierung" eingefügt

Changelog V 1.1.0.0
- Getestet mit TestRunner_public (GIANTS). (Fehlerfrei!)
- Flachbett angepasst
- Zuladung geänder. 10 und 20 Euro Paletten.
- Rücklichter ans Flachbett angebracht
- Anhängerkupplung mit Verbindungen angebracht. (Achtung, leider funktioniert der Autoload mit Anhänger nur bei dem LKW, nicht beim Anhänger!)
- Logos ans Flachbett angebracht
- Neues Store Bild
- Neues Icon Bild
- Beschreibung in der modDesc angepasst

Changelog V 1.0.8.0
- Farbauswahl
- Übersetzung in die modDesc verlagert

            ]]>
        </de>

        <fr> <![CDATA[
Pour la fonction autochargeur de palettes, la "Paletten Autoloader Spezialisierung" d'Achimobil est nécessaire.

MACK Super-Liner 6x4 V2 avec fonction autochargeur de palettes vous facilite le travail avec les productions et les nombreuses palettes. 
Jusqu'à 24 palettes Euro peuvent être transportées en une seule tournée. 

Le MACK dispose d'un attelage de remorque, il est donc possible d'y atteler des remorques, ce qui augmente la quantité d'euro-palettes à transporter en fonction de la remorque.

Les palettes Euro, les citernes de liquide, les palettes BigBag, les balles rondes de coton et les palettes Euro surdimensionnées peuvent être chargées par la spécialisation Autoloader de palettes.

La charge utile peut être choisie dans la boutique entre 12 et 24 palettes Euro. 
Le choix de la couleur vous permet de personnaliser le MACK selon vos souhaits.

Changelog V 1.2.0.0
- Testé avec TestRunner_public (GIANTS). (sans erreur !)
- Surface de chargement agrandie
- Ajustement de la surface de chargement pour l'autoload
- Déclenchement de l'autoload déplacé plus en avant à cause de la remorque
- Chargement modifié palettes de 12 et 24 euros.
- Attelage de remorque avec connexions déplacé plus loin vers l'arrière. (Autoload fonctionne maintenant avec la remorque.)
- Feux latéraux ajoutés.
- Ajout des dépendances de "Spécialisation de l'autochargeur de palettes".

Changelog V 1.1.0.0
- Testé avec TestRunner_public (GIANTS). (sans erreur !)
- Adaptation de la table plate
- Chargement modifié. Palettes de 10 et 20 euros.
- Feux arrière fixés sur le plateau
- Attelage de remorque avec connexions. (Attention, malheureusement, l'autoload avec remorque ne fonctionne que pour le camion, pas pour la remorque !)
- Logos fixés sur le plateau
- Nouvelle image Store
- Nouvelle image d'icône
- Description adaptée dans le modDesc

Changelog V 1.0.8.0
- Choix des couleurs
- Traduction déplacée dans le modDesc
            ]]>
        </fr>

        <it> <![CDATA[
La "Specializzazione Pallet Autoloader" di Achimobil è necessaria per la funzione Pallet Autoloader.

Il MACK Super-Liner 6x4 V2 con funzione di caricatore automatico di pallet facilita il lavoro con le produzioni e i numerosi pallet. 
Fino a 24 europallet possono essere trasportati in un solo viaggio. 

Il MACK ha un gancio di traino, quindi i rimorchi possono essere accoppiati, il che aumenta la quantità di europallet da trasportare a seconda del rimorchio.

Gli europallet, i serbatoi di liquidi, i pallet BigBag, le balle rotonde di cotone e gli europallet sovradimensionati possono essere caricati dalla specializzazione Pallet Autoloader.

Il carico utile può essere selezionato in negozio tra 12 e 24 Euro pallet. 
Con la scelta del colore, potete progettare il MACK secondo i vostri desideri.

Changelog V 1.2.0.0
- Testato con TestRunner_public (GIANTS). (Senza errori!)
- Area di carico allargata
- Zona di carico adattata per l'autocaricamento
- Grilletto di autocaricamento spostato più avanti a causa del rimorchio
- Carico utile cambiato 12 e 24 Euro pallet.
- Gancio di traino con attacchi spostati più indietro. (Autoload ora funziona con il rimorchio).
- Luci laterali montate.
- Dipendenze di "Specializzazione Pallet Autoloader" inserite

Changelog V 1.1.0.0
- Testato con TestRunner_public (GIANTS). (Senza errori!)
- Flatbed adattato
- La capacità di carico è cambiata. Pallet da 10 e 20 euro.
- Luci posteriori attaccate al pianale.
- Gancio di traino con attacchi attaccati. (Attenzione, purtroppo l'autoload con rimorchio funziona solo con il camion, non con il rimorchio).
- Loghi attaccati al pianale
- Nuova immagine del negozio
- Nuova immagine dell'icona
- Descrizione nel modDesc adattata

Changelog V 1.0.8.0
- Selezione del colore
- La traduzione è stata spostata nel modDesc
            ]]>
        </it>
    </description>

    <iconFilename>icon_superliner1979_AL.png</iconFilename>

    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <storeItems>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="superliner1979_AL.xml"/>
    </storeItems>

    <dependencies>
        <dependency>FS22_aPalletAutoLoader</dependency>
    </dependencies>

    <brands>
        <brand name="MEMDOR" title="MEMDOR" image="brand.icon.dds"/>
    </brands>

    <vehicleTypes>
        <type name="PalletAutoLoaderTruck" parent="baseDrivable" filename="$dataS/scripts/vehicles/Vehicle.lua">
            <specialization name="FS22_aPalletAutoLoader.aPalletAutoLoader"/>
            <specialization name="tensionBelts"/>
        </type>
    </vehicleTypes>

    <l10n>
        <text name="function_PalletAutoload_Truck">
            <en>Truck with Autoload for pallets.</en>
            <de>Truck mit Autoload für verschiedene Paletten.</de>
            <fr>Camion avec Autoload pour palettes.</fr>
            <it>Camion con Autoload per pallet.</it>
        </text>
        <text name="type_PalletAutoload_Truck">
            <en>Pallet Autoload</en>
            <de>Paletten Autoloader</de>
            <fr>Autochargeur de palettes</fr>
            <it>Caricatore automatico di pallet</it>
        </text>
        <text name="unit_PalletAutoload_Truck">
            <en>Pallets</en>
            <de>Paletten</de>
            <fr>Palettes</fr>
            <it>Pallets</it>
        </text>
        <text name="configuration_aPalletAutoloader_Mack">
            <en>Maximum payload</en>
            <de>Maximale Zuladdung</de>
            <fr>Charge maximale</fr>
            <it>Carico utile massimo</it>
        </text>
        <text name="configuration_Pallet_12">
            <en>12 Euro pallets</en>
            <de>12 Euro-Paletten</de>
            <fr>12 palettes Euro</fr>
            <it>12 Euro pallet</it>
        </text>
        <text name="configuration_Pallet_24">
            <en>24 Euro pallets</en>
            <de>24 Euro-Paletten</de>
            <fr>24 palettes Euro</fr>
            <it>24 Euro pallet</it>
        </text>
        <text name="configuration_Pallet_36">
            <en>36 Euro pallets</en>
            <de>36 Euro-Paletten</de>
            <fr>36 palettes Euro</fr>
            <it>36 Euro pallet</it>
        </text>
    </l10n>

</modDesc>
